

CONTACT INFO



García, Nuevo León, MEX.



rolando.code@gmail.com

LANGUAGE

Spanish

English

EXPERTISE

Net Framework

Dot Net core

Dot Net 5, 6

MS SQL Server

GIT

Typescript

Angular

MORE ABOUT ME



You can visit my page and portfolio scanning the QR or you can go to github page https://bit.ly/3XMGc49

Rolando Domínguez

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ENGINEER

SUMMARY

I am a software developer since 2015, that enjoys backend development with .NET technology. Also I like develop with Angular on the client side. I love write clean code, I think it's a fully creative activity and whole art.

(Actually I really love backend development more than the frontend.. don't tell to the frontend, it would break his heart)

WORK EXPERIENCE

AGILE THOUGHT- Dot net Senior and consultant developer

- <u>- Senior software engineer at Brierley client.</u> 2021-2022 Net framework code maintenance. REST API conversion from SOAP. Code enhancements and code reviews in github. Oracle DB scripts.
- <u>Senior software engineer at VyStar client</u>. 2022-2023. Net core code maintenance. ASP Net MVC pages refactors and maintenance. Net core small modules migration to net 6. Using of MS Azure pipelines

AXOSNET- Dot net core, dot net framework and Angular Sr. developer 2019-2021

Net framework to Net core 3.1 migration (from scratch. Invoice verification software **API design and creation** for México, Costa Rica, Colombia and Perú Internal tools in **Angular and AngularJS. Technical designs** for API solutions in **net framework/core** and **SQL server**. AWS **cloudwatch**, **EC2** instances, load balancers

Bind ERP- Technical and software support lead. Semi Sr. developer 2018-2019

APIs Rest and Web Services integration for Mexican invoicing. Technical staff recruiter. **ASP Net and Web forms** migrations to **AngularJS** and **Typescript**. Microsoft **Azure app services settings and deployments**

Bind ERP – Jr. dot Net Framework and AngularJS developer

2015-2018

2021- PRESENT

SQL server production DB management. Computer building and maintenance, local networks configuration. Support apps creation with **AngularJS** with **Typescript** and **Net Framework**.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Master degree in Information Technology Engineering

2016-2018

School of mechanical and electrical engineering. UANL.

Computer Science degree

2010-2015

School of Physics and Mathematics UANL

CERTIFICATES

- Using SOLID principles to Write Better Code
- Creating professional web APIs with .NET 6
- Software Engineering 101: Use Software Engineering to Plan and Build Amazing Software + Learn SCRUM Framework!